jSONObj = [{
    "question": "The tallest mountain on Earth",
    "answers": ["Cho Oyu", "Everest", "Annapurna", "Rainier"],
    "correct_answer": "Everest",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the capital city of Cuba?",
    "answers": ["Madrid", "Havana", "Puerto Rico", "Paris"],
    "correct_answer": "Havana",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the closest planet to Earth?",
    "answers": ["Jupiter", "Uran", "Mars", "Venus"],
    "correct_answer": "Venus",
    "timeInSeconds": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "The biggest mammal in the world",
    "answers": ["Blue Whale", "Crocodile", "Elephant", "Rhino"],
    "correct_answer": "Blue Whale",
    "timeInSeconds": 11
  },
  {
    "question": "The title of rulers in ancient Egypt",
    "answers": ["King", "Emperor", "Pharaoh", "Duke"],
    "correct_answer": "Pharaoh",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "How many meters in one kilometer?",
    "answers": ["1,000", "10,000", "100", "5,280"],
    "correct_answer": "1,000",
    "timeInSeconds": 7
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of these countries depicts Sun on the national flag?",
    "answers": ["Japan", "Sweden", "Brazil", "Ukraine"],
    "correct_answer": "Japan",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "How many colonies formed the United States in 1776?",
    "answers": ["9", "11", "13", "15"],
    "correct_answer": "13",
    "timeInSeconds": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "Greenland, the biggest island in the world, is a part of this country",
    "answers": ["Denmark", "Iceland", "Norway", "Canada"],
    "correct_answer": "Denmark",
    "timeInSeconds": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "The Statue of Liberty was a gift from this country to the USA",
    "answers": ["UK", "Spain", "Mexico", "France"],
    "correct_answer": "France",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Count Dracula originated from Transylvania which is the part of this modern country",
    "answers": ["Romania", "Poland", "Turkey", "Macedonia"],
    "correct_answer": "Romania",
    "timeInSeconds": 12
  },
  {
    "question": "These birds are famous for having wingspans greater than 10 feet (3.3 m)",
    "answers": ["Bald eagle", "Albatross", "White Owl", "Emu"],
    "correct_answer": "Albatross",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "Kiwi birds are native to ...",
    "answers": ["Australia", "Austria", "New Zeland", "Argentina"],
    "correct_answer": "New Zeland",
    "timeInSeconds": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "Currency used by Germany, Netherlands and France",
    "answers": ["US Dollars", "Euro", "Mark", "Frank"],
    "correct_answer": "Euro",
    "timeInSeconds": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "The biggest state of the USA by area",
    "answers": ["Texas", "Montana", "California", "Alaska"],
    "correct_answer": "Alaska",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "The biggest state of the USA by population",
    "answers": ["California", "New York", "Texas", "Florida"],
    "correct_answer": "California",
    "timeInSeconds": 10
  },
  {
    "question": "The distance from Earth to the sun is called an ...",
    "answers": ["Astronomical unit", "Astronomical mile", "Kilometer", "Nautical mile"],
    "correct_answer": "Astronomical unit",
    "timeInSeconds": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "The first national park of the USA",
    "answers": ["Mount Rainier", "Sequoia", "Yosemite", "Yellowstone"],
    "correct_answer": "Yellowstone",
    "timeInSeconds": 9
  },
  {
    "question": "HaleakalƒÅ National Park is located in the state of ...",
    "answers": ["New Mexico", "Hawaii", "California", "Arizona"],
    "correct_answer": "Hawaii",
    "timeInSeconds": 8
  },
  {
    "question": "The largest known extant fish species is ...",
    "answers": ["Whale shark", "Blue whale", "Orca", "Beluga sturgeon"],
    "correct_answer": "Whale shark",
    "timeInSeconds": 14
  }
  
];